twalky.com 2011-05-21

# Twalky About Us

**Privacy**

     Twalky takes your privacy very seriously. We have made our privacy policy easier to find and easier to read. Welcome your questions and feedback on our privacy policy. 

     **1.Personal Information**  
     At Twalky, we are fully committed to respecting your privacy and to protecting any information you provide to us. We treat both privacy and security as a priority and make every effort to ensure that all the information provided by you is protected. This Privacy Policy (the"Policy") is designed to respect and protect the privacy of all visitors to the Website and is intended to inform you about the way that we treat your personal data. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, gender, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

     **2.Information Collection And Use**   
     Twalky uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

     **3.Information Sharing And Disclosure**  
     We will not share your information with any third parties, except that we may disclose your personal information to third parties who perform services for us, such as third-party credit card processors or prize fulfillment entities. We do not control the activities of such third-party vendors. While we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as Twalky, we will take all reasonable precautions under the circumstances to ensure the protection of your personal information. 

     **4\. Confidentiality And Security**  
     We take all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data. All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through our Web sites. Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. 

     **5\. Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
     We may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Twalky account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Back
